<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Win7 on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/tags/win7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Win7 on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 11:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/tags/win7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Opera 10.5 Beta and Windows 7 Integration</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2010/02/15/opera-10-5-beta-and-windows-7-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 11:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2010/02/15/opera-10-5-beta-and-windows-7-integration/</guid>
      <description>Opera 10.5 Beta is out and it&amp;rsquo;s very impressive, and looks pretty stunning due to its Windows 7 integration.
One thing I don&amp;rsquo;t really like is how it shows all the tabs using Aero Peek when you click it in the Task Bar.
You can turn this off:
 Type &amp;ldquo;opera:config&amp;rdquo; in the address bar and hit Enter Scroll down to User Prefs and expand it, or type in &amp;ldquo;Windows 7&amp;#8243; in the search box Untick the &amp;ldquo;Use Windows 7 Taskbar Thumbnails&amp;rdquo; setting Click Save Restart Opera  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing WinPcap &amp;amp; WC3Banlist on Windows 7</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/06/08/installing-winpcap-wc3banlist-on-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 19:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/06/08/installing-winpcap-wc3banlist-on-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>I had a bit of trouble getting WC3Banlist (mainly due to its dependency on WinPcap) on Windows 7 This is working on Windows 7 RC1, with User Acount Control (UAC) on (set to Default) I did quite a few things when troubleshooting so it&amp;rsquo;s hard to replicate the exact steps, but here&amp;rsquo;s some instructions on how I have it set up now: Install WinPcap  Download WinPcap 4.1 Right click the downloaded installer exe and choose Properties Go to the Compatibility tab In Compatibility mode, Tick &amp;ldquo;Run this program in compatibility mode for:&amp;rdquo; and choose Windows Vista (Service Pack 2) from the drop-down Tick &amp;ldquo;Run this program as an administrator&amp;rdquo; in Privilege Level Hit OK Run the exe and go through the normal installation  Install WC3Banlist  Download WC3Banlist Right click the installation file and choose Run as administrator Untick &amp;ldquo;Install WinPcap 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving your precious user profile and documents to another folder on another drive in Windows 7</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/05/26/moving-your-precious-user-profile-and-documents-to-another-folder-on-another-drive-in-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/05/26/moving-your-precious-user-profile-and-documents-to-another-folder-on-another-drive-in-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I learned long ago was to always have more than 1 drive or have my single drive partitioned. You keep your programs and operating system on the C drive. On your D drive goes all your data, downloads and anything that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to vanish on you suddenly. A couple of advantages of this are:  This keeps the C drive quite lean if you want to make an image of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>