<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Misc on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Misc on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 01:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris &amp;#038; London photos</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/11/06/paris-london-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/11/06/paris-london-photos/</guid>
      <description>Elinor and Julia visited from New Zealand, and we went to Paris and hung out in London for a few days. I&amp;rsquo;ve posted some photos on Facebook but I&amp;rsquo;ll try to blog something about it at some point. Was good fun, and nice to see Els and get some travel done (even if it was to Paris again).
So I&amp;rsquo;m ready to get cracking into work again and get prepared for my return to New Zealand which is really only weeks away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris &amp;amp; London photos</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/11/06/paris-london-photos-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/11/06/paris-london-photos-2/</guid>
      <description>Elinor and Julia visited from New Zealand, and we went to Paris and hung out in London for a few days. I&amp;rsquo;ve posted some photos on Facebook but I&amp;rsquo;ll try to blog something about it at some point. Was good fun, and nice to see Els and get some travel done (even if it was to Paris again). So I&amp;rsquo;m ready to get cracking into work again and get prepared for my return to New Zealand which is really only weeks away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning to New Zealand in December</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/19/returning-to-new-zealand-in-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 14:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/19/returning-to-new-zealand-in-december/</guid>
      <description>Talking to the flatties, everyone&amp;rsquo;s quite keen to come back to New Zealand a few months earlier than our visa expiration.
Aaron and Renee want to get back for a wedding and their legendary gran&amp;rsquo;s birthday.
This suits me, as I&amp;rsquo;m broke, and won&amp;rsquo;t achieve anything staying here much longer.
I will settle on a date soon so I can book the flight. I&amp;rsquo;d like to come back for xmas for sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Visa News</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/26/london-visa-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 12:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/26/london-visa-news/</guid>
      <description>News on the London front! I still have quite a few months left on my visa, but my 12 months of allowed work are nearly used up. This means I can still stay in London but won&amp;rsquo;t be allowed to work.
My job wants to keep me on, so I will basically have to come back to NZ for a short time soon. From there, work will arrange sponsorship for me, and I will then re-enter London on a work visa that lasts for up to 2 years and is then renewable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Tea Pills are like, whoa</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/12/green-tea-pills-are-like-whoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 22:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/12/green-tea-pills-are-like-whoa/</guid>
      <description>So my workmate offers me a green tea pill this afternoon. I like green tea, and a green tea pill sounds healthy and good enough (if not a strange way to be getting your green tea).
He then checks on the bottle, and notes a warning saying &amp;ldquo;Do not take after 4pm&amp;rdquo; and tells me about it after I&amp;rsquo;ve already downed the pill.
Turns out the pill has got caffeine, guarana and every other possible legal stimulant and anti-oxidant you could name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh hai</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/09/hello-world-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 02:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/09/hello-world-2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while! The old blog is broken while I updated the software, but for now I&amp;rsquo;ve plumped for a good old WordPress install.
A lot&amp;rsquo;s happened since the last post on the old blog, which was posted just before I went to Cardiff to watch the All Blacks choke in the World Cup semi final.
Well New Zealand just beat Ireland on the weekend in their first game since the ill-fated World Cup campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>