<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World of Warcraft on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World of Warcraft on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 20:14:51 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ataldazar</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/ataldazar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/ataldazar/</guid>
      <description>Notable Trash  If Dazar&amp;rsquo;ai Confessors get a Bwonsamdi&amp;rsquo;s Mantle cast off, drag trash out of the bubble, as it makes their casts un-interruptible Interrupt Dazar&amp;rsquo;ai Augur&amp;rsquo;s Fiery Enchant (exploding fire circles under party members&amp;rsquo; feet) For Shieldbearers of Zul, use Hammer of Justice or Blinding Light to interrupt their Bulwark of Juju   Priestess Alun&amp;rsquo;za  Use activate mitigation, perhaps a cooldown, for Gilded Claws Tank her near a Tainted Blood puddle Step into Tainted Blood just before she casts Transfusion Stun and kill Spirits of Gold so they don&amp;rsquo;t absorb Tainted Blood puddles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ElvUI Updater</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/elvui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/elvui/</guid>
      <description>Download Latest Version: https://github.com/DavidMoore/ElvUI.Updater/releases/download/0.9.1/Setup.exe
 Releases: https://github.com/DavidMoore/ElvUI.Updater/releases/latest Support: https://github.com/DavidMoore/ElvUI.Updater/issues  What is ElvUI? ElvUI is a beautiful, minimalist, highly customizable user interface suite for World of Warcraft.
I have been using ElvUI for a few years now, and would recommend it to newcomers or veterans.
You can find out more about ElvUI here: https://www.tukui.org/download.php?ui=elvui
ElvUI Updater ElvUI is not available from the Twitch add-on manager, so you normally have to download and update it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freehold</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/freehold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/freehold/</guid>
      <description>Talents Choose Blessing of Protection to put on party members if fixated by ground shark on 2nd boss (save for healer ideally)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings&#39; Rest</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/kings-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/kings-rest/</guid>
      <description> Dazar, The First King  Use Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to break the fear  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Profiles</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/profile/</guid>
      <description> Links  Armory Profile raider.io Profile  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythic&#43;</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/mythicplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/mythicplus/</guid>
      <description>Loot  Weekly Chest contains 1 item Azerite pieces only drop from the Weekly Chest No gear or talent changes in Mythic+ You can zone out, change gear and/or talents, then zone back in You can now bonus roll for loot in Mythic+     Keystone Level End of Dungeon Weekly Chest Azerite Armor (Weekly Chest)     Mythic 2 345 355 340   Mythic 3 345 355 340   Mythic 4 350 360 355   Mythic 5 355 360 355   Mythic 6 355 365 355   Mythic 7 360 370 370   Mythic 8 365 370 370   Mythic 9 365 375 370   Mythic 10+ 370 380 385    Affix Schedule Affix 1 Affix 2 Affix 3 Fortified Sanguine Necrotic Tyrannical Bursting Skittish Fortified Teeming Quaking Tyrannical Raging Necrotic Fortified Bolstering Skittish Tyrannical Teeming Volcanic Fortified Sanguine Grievous Tyrannical Bolstering Explosive Fortified Bursting Quaking Tyrannical Raging Volcanic Fortified Teeming Explosive Tyrannical Bolstering Grievous</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paladin Macros</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/macros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/macros/</guid>
      <description>Avenger&amp;rsquo;s Shield Casts at mouseover enemy, focus target enemy or current target If you&amp;rsquo;re in PvP and holding CTRL, then enable Shield of Virtue (AOE silence) before throwing shield
 #showtooltip Avenger&#39;s Shield /cast [mod:ctrl] Shield of Virtue /cast [@mouseover,harm,nodead][@focus,harm,nodead][@target,harm,nodead]Avenger&#39;s Shield  Rebuke Kick / interrupt your mouseover target, focus target or selected target (in that priority order)
 #showtooltip Rebuke /stopcasting /cast [@mouseover,harm,nodead][@focus,harm,nodead][@target,harm,nodead] Rebuke  Judgment Judges your mouseover target if they&amp;rsquo;re an enemy, enemy focus target or finally your target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paladin PvP Guide</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/pvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/pvp/</guid>
      <description> References    Name Description Authors Updated     Skillcapped Paladin PvP Guide       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protection Paladin</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/protection/</guid>
      <description>Stats Item Level &amp;gt; Haste &amp;gt; Mastery &amp;gt;= Versatility &amp;gt; Crit
Enchants &amp;amp; Gems  Weapon Enchant: Quick Navigation Ring Enchant: Haste Gems: 1 x Strength then Haste  Consumables  Flask: Strength Battle Potion: Potion of Bursting Blood for Single Target, Battle Potion of Strength for Multi-Target Food: Feast or Haste  Trinkets Azerite Traits   RankDefensiveOffensive STAOESTAOE OuterMiddleInnerOuterMiddleInnerOuterMiddleInnerOuterMiddleInner   S+ TierGemhideSoaring Shield S TierAblative ShieldingGemhide Inspiring Vanguard x1Inspiring Vanguard Ablative Shielding A TierCrystalline CarapaceCrystalline Carapace Impassive VisageBulwark of Light Meticulous SchemingImpassive Visage TradewindsBulwark of the Masses Bulwark of LightAvenger’s Might Life SpeedTradewinds Shimmering HavenIncite the Pack Blood SiphonBlood Siphon Avenger’s MightLife Speed Shimmering Haven B TierSoaring ShieldAzerite Veins Azerite VeinsResounding Protection Resounding ProtectionMeticulous Scheming Archive of the TitansArchive of the Titans On My WayOn My Way Concentrated MendingUnstable Catalyst Strength in Numbers   Defensive Gemhide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raid: Uldir</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/uldir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/uldir/</guid>
      <description>Loot Levels    Difficulty Item Level     LFR 340   Normal 355   Heroic 370   Mythic 385     Weapons can only Warforge (+5 or +10) Azerite Armor cannot Warforge or Titanforge  Boss Loot  BoEAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution Wrist Haste / Mast Hands Crit / Haste Wing 1 TalocAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution Trinket: +Int, aoe damage proc2H Str Mace Crit/Haste Wrists Vers/Crit Legs: Haste/Mastery MOTHERAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution HeadArchive of the TitansLaser MatrixAzerite VeinsElemental WhirlEphemeral RecoveryResounding ProtectionImpassive VisageInspiring VanguardGrace of the JusticarDivine Right Offhand Crit/Vers Waist Mast/Crit Ring: Crit/Haste Zek&#39;vozAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution 1H Ver/Mast MaceTrinket: +Str, Damage proc (cone) Legs: Vers/Mastery Feet: Haste/Vers Ring: Mastery/Crit Fetid DevourerAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution 1H Axe1H Axe Crit/Vers Hands Crit/Vers Cloak: Haste/Mastery VectisAzerite ArmourRole TraitsDefensive TraitsProtectionHolyRetribution VectisChestArchive of the TitansLaser MatrixStrength In NumbersUnstable FlamesWoundbinderJudicious DefenseBreaking DawnRelentless Inquisitor Shield Crit/VersTrinket: +Int; Active ability adds 3k to next 5 direct heals on target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings &amp; Performance</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/performance/</guid>
      <description>System &amp;gt; Graphics Always have these on:
Project Textures (SET projectedTextures &amp;quot;1.000000&amp;quot;)
Projected textures are usually used for ground visual effects for important mechanics in dungeons and raids; if you don&amp;rsquo;t have them enabled, you will often not be able to see these mechanics and die to them.
Anti-Aliasing:
System &amp;gt; Advanced    Setting Description Recommendation     Triple Buffering Smooths our framerate and eliminates tearing, but introduces input lag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrine of the Storm</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/shrine-of-the-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/shrine-of-the-storm/</guid>
      <description> Notable Trash  Abyss Dwellers: Use Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to drop stacks or prevent application of Rip Mind  Lord Stormsong  Make sure you have Avenger&amp;rsquo;s Shield ready to interrupt the Void Bolt he will cast immediately after Awaken the Void  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siege of Boralus</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/siege-of-boralus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/siege-of-boralus/</guid>
      <description> Notable Trash  Bilge Rat Buccaneer: Use Blinding Light to disorient them when they try to cast Banana Rampage Ashvane Invader: Use Divine Shield or Blessing of Spellwarding to drop stacks of Stinging Venom Coating  Sergeant Bainbridge/Chopper Redhook  Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to immune bombs if they&amp;rsquo;re about to go off  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple of Sethraliss</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/temple-of-sethraliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/temple-of-sethraliss/</guid>
      <description> Notable Trash  Faithless Tender: Interrupt Drain  Merektha  Hammer of Justice can free party members from A Knot of Snakes Move adds out of Dust Cloud  Galvazzt  Use Blessing of Spellwarding to soak Galvanize, or Divine Shield to remove stacks if necessary  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MOTHERLODE!!</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/the-motherlode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/the-motherlode/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Underrot</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/the-underrot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/the-underrot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tol Dagor</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/tol-dagor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/tol-dagor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waycrest Manor</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/waycrest-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/dungeon/waycrest-manor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>