<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Battle for Azeroth Dungeons on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Battle for Azeroth Dungeons on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 19:41:07 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ataldazar</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/ataldazar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/ataldazar/</guid>
      <description>Notable Trash  If Dazar&amp;rsquo;ai Confessors get a Bwonsamdi&amp;rsquo;s Mantle cast off, drag trash out of the bubble, as it makes their casts un-interruptible Interrupt Dazar&amp;rsquo;ai Augur&amp;rsquo;s Fiery Enchant (exploding fire circles under party members&amp;rsquo; feet) For Shieldbearers of Zul, use Hammer of Justice or Blinding Light to interrupt their Bulwark of Juju   Priestess Alun&amp;rsquo;za  Use activate mitigation, perhaps a cooldown, for Gilded Claws Tank her near a Tainted Blood puddle Step into Tainted Blood just before she casts Transfusion Stun and kill Spirits of Gold so they don&amp;rsquo;t absorb Tainted Blood puddles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freehold</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/freehold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/freehold/</guid>
      <description>Talents Choose Blessing of Protection to put on party members if fixated by ground shark on 2nd boss (save for healer ideally)
Skycap&amp;rsquo;n Kragg
Spread from your party members, kick his healing spell. When he dismounts from his bird, the bird will come back from the edge of the arena and charge through. Try to avoid this bird.
Council o&amp;rsquo; Captains
When friendly has big barrel on his head, kill barrel, don&amp;rsquo;t stand in AOE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings&#39; Rest</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/kings-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/kings-rest/</guid>
      <description>Dazar, The First King  Use Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to break the fear  The Golden Serpent
When you have orange DOT on yourself go away from boss it will make a pool appear beneath you at the end of the DOT, try to stack those pools at the same place, important cause thats where the adds will come from, don&amp;rsquo;t let adds reach boss, use your slows and stuns, dont stay melee range when boss is doing tornado around him</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrine of the Storm</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/shrine-of-the-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/shrine-of-the-storm/</guid>
      <description>Notable Trash  Abyss Dwellers: Use Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to drop stacks or prevent application of Rip Mind  Lord Stormsong  Make sure you have Avenger&amp;rsquo;s Shield ready to interrupt the Void Bolt he will cast immediately after Awaken the Void  Aqu&amp;rsquo;Sirr
Dont stand near edges, you don&amp;rsquo;t wanna get knocked back and die, avoid his charge, avoid blue aoe on the ground. When he splits into 3 water elementals, try to focus fire them one by one, dont spread DPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siege of Boralus</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/siege-of-boralus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/siege-of-boralus/</guid>
      <description>Notable Trash  Bilge Rat Buccaneer: Use Blinding Light to disorient them when they try to cast Banana Rampage Ashvane Invader: Use Divine Shield or Blessing of Spellwarding to drop stacks of Stinging Venom Coating  Sergeant Bainbridge/Chopper Redhook  Blessing of Spellwarding or Divine Shield to immune bombs if they&amp;rsquo;re about to go off  Sergeant Bainbridge
Don&amp;rsquo;t walk in bombs on the ground. If the boss is chasing after you, make him run through bombs on ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple of Sethraliss</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/temple-of-sethraliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/temple-of-sethraliss/</guid>
      <description>Notable Trash  Faithless Tender: Interrupt Drain  Merektha  Hammer of Justice can free party members from A Knot of Snakes Move adds out of Dust Cloud  Galvazzt  Use Blessing of Spellwarding to soak Galvanize, or Divine Shield to remove stacks if necessary  Adderis and Aspix
Hit the one that doesnt have Lightning Shield (it will change so be careful), if you have electricity debuff on you go away from friends, spread out when he is doing ninja electricity charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MOTHERLODE!!</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/the-motherlode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/the-motherlode/</guid>
      <description>Coin-Operated Crowd Pummeler
When he drops grenades on the floor, go throw those back at him. You need to be facing him while in front of the grenade. When he turns facing you and starts canalizing a spell, move so you&amp;rsquo;re on his side or back.
Azerokk
Use totems to CC 2 elementals before the fight. If you have big red eyes on you run away from elementals. When they become very shiny they take 150% more damage but they also hit harder, so kill them with range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Underrot</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/the-underrot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/the-underrot/</guid>
      <description>Elder Leaxa
I&amp;rsquo;m sure there is something this boss does apart from dying fast, but I havent found it yet.
Cragmaw the Infested
Go away from the direction he&amp;rsquo;s facing when he&amp;rsquo;s charging. Go step on red things on ground so it doesnt spawn little adds that will stack a nasty dot on you.
Sporecaller Zancha
He will spawn green shrooms around him. When you have a big arrow above your head, go stand near those shrooms (but not IN it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tol Dagor</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/tol-dagor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/tol-dagor/</guid>
      <description>The Sand Queen
When you have big arrow on your head, go away from friends. Dont walk into stuff she spawns on the ground. Kill adds quickly.
Jes Howlis
When he starts casting Flashing Daggers go behind a wall. When he runs away follow him and finish him. Use your stuns / slows on adds.
Kingh Captain Valyri
If you have red fire dot on you, dont go near barrels, you will explode them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waycrest Manor</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/waycrest-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/games/wow/bfa/dungeon/waycrest-manor/</guid>
      <description>Heartsbane Triad
One of the 3 bosses will be bigger than the others. Do damage to this one. Then it will change. So change target, you need to hit the one that is bigger than the others always. Keep moving when you have shadow dot on you to avoid stacking it.
Soulbound Goliath
When he imprisons one of your friends kill the thing. Don&amp;rsquo;t stand on the fire. If you&amp;rsquo;re a tank, when boss reaches high stacks you might wanna pop defensive CDs or kite him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>