<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unreal Tournament on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/unreal-tournament/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unreal Tournament on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 23:26:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/unreal-tournament/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix the missing right click menu for Unreal Engine Projects (.uproject)</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2014/09/05/fix-the-missing-right-click-menu-for-unreal-engine-projects-uproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 23:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2014/09/05/fix-the-missing-right-click-menu-for-unreal-engine-projects-uproject/</guid>
      <description>When you right click on an Unreal Engine project file (.uproject), these is the kind of menu options you should see:
But what do you do if you only see this? :
The right click context menu is set up via the Windows Registry.
You could get someone to export their working keys for you, but their installation paths may be different to yours.
I’ve created a Windows batch file instead which will:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Tournament 3 (UT3) Protocol Registry Fix for launching UT3 links</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2014/07/19/unreal-tournament-3-ut3-protocol-registry-fix-for-launching-ut3-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 19:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2014/07/19/unreal-tournament-3-ut3-protocol-registry-fix-for-launching-ut3-links/</guid>
      <description>UT3, at least installed via Steam, doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to register a URI scheme in Windows so that you can create links to UT3 servers, as was possible in earlier versions of Unreal Tournament.
This can be fixed by manually adding a ut3 protocol to the Windows registry.
Instructions  Download the initial registry fix, but don&amp;rsquo;t merge it yet: Download UT3 Protocol registry fix Open it with a text editor such as Notepad Change the install location to make where you have UT3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>