<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 21:55:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/categories/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies: The Expendables, The Green Hornet, Dimension</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/04/17/movies-the-expendables-the-green-hornet-dimension/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 21:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/04/17/movies-the-expendables-the-green-hornet-dimension/</guid>
      <description>e cool looking movies on the distant horizon. Sylvester Stallone, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Jason Statham, Mickey Rourke, Dolph Lundgren, Jet Li, Randy Couture, Steve Austin, Eric Roberts, Terry Crews, Danny Trejo&amp;hellip; The Expendables cast is wicked! This could be an awesome unabashed 80s-style action movie if the script is good enough and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take itself too seriously. Then we have Michel Gondry directing Seth Rogen and Stephen Chow in The Green Hornet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For people who&amp;#226;&amp;#8364;&amp;#8482;ve read Watchmen the &amp;#226;&amp;#8364;&amp;#339;graphic novel&amp;#226;&amp;#8364; and watched the movie</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/03/06/for-people-whove-read-watchmen-the-graphic-novel-and-watched-the-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 00:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/03/06/for-people-whove-read-watchmen-the-graphic-novel-and-watched-the-movie/</guid>
      <description>Otherwise, spoilers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Future Alternate Ending</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/02/25/back-to-the-future-alternate-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 09:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/02/25/back-to-the-future-alternate-ending/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new Jean-Claude Van Damme movie worth seeing?</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/13/a-new-jean-claude-van-damme-movie-worth-seeing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 12:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/13/a-new-jean-claude-van-damme-movie-worth-seeing/</guid>
      <description>Jean-Claude Van Damme playing himself in an action comedy? The trailer actually looks half good, and it has positive reviews so far.
 Jean-Claude finds himself out of money, fighting for custody of his daughter and losing every good action role to Steven Seagal. In an attempt to escape, the aging star walks away from his shrinking spotlight and returns home to his native Brussels. But when he is thrown into a real-life hostage situation, everyone sees a side of Van Damme they’ve never seen before as he takes on the police, battles the perpetrators and creates a media firestorm that captures the attention of the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond &#34;The King of Kong&#34;</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/13/beyond-the-king-of-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 10:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/06/13/beyond-the-king-of-kong/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched The King of Kong, I highly recommend it.
It&amp;rsquo;s a documentary about 2 men from entirely different backgrounds and circumstances facing off for the world record of the classic arcade game Donkey Kong. It might sound boring, but it&amp;rsquo;s 1% about the game, and 99% about human behaviour, obssession, celebrity, redemption, underdog versus establishment. Very entertaining and rivetting. (97% rating on Rotten Tomatoes)
Anyway, I can&amp;rsquo;t get over the fact that the &amp;ldquo;villain&amp;rdquo; of the documentary &amp;#8211; Billy Mitchell &amp;#8211; reminds me so much of Michael Scott from The Office.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>