<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 19:40:44 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows File Sharing</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/windows-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 22:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/windows-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to share your files on the lan without requiring people to log in or join your Home Group?
The following instructions are for Windows 7 and the NTFS (default and recommended) file system.
Turn off Simple File Sharing From the Control Panel, search for Folder Options and open it (or from an Explorer window, go to the menu Organize &amp;gt; Folder and search options
Go to the View tab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/bootable-usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/bootable-usb/</guid>
      <description>Making a Windows Bootable USB Drive Format the USB drive and make it bootable Replace ? with the letter of your USB Drive below
diskpart list disk select disk ? clean create partition primary select partition 1 active format fs=ntfs quick label=&amp;quot;Windows Setup&amp;quot; exit  Make it boot Windows 10 Installer Copy over Windows 10 files Use 7-zip to extract the contents of the .iso to the USB drive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/regfree-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/regfree-com/</guid>
      <description>Registration-Free COM Troubleshooting The application has failed to start because its side-by-side configuration is incorrect. When launching the application, you may see a dialog stating The application has failed to start because its side-by-side configuration is incorrect. Please see the application event log or user the command-line sxstrace.exe tool for more detail.
You can create a batch file to make it easier to run, parse and view the SxSTrace:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Maintenance</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/wiki/windows/maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Deployment Image Servicing and Management tool (DISM) DISM can be used to mount and service a Windows image from a .wim file, .vhd file, or a .vhdx file or, in some cases, to update a running operating system.
You can use DISM to do various cleanup operations related to installed components, updates and service packs.
Remove Service Pack backup components after Service Pack installation After installing a Service Pack, you can clean up backed up components:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>