<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sql on Sad Robot</title>
    <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/tags/sql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sql on Sad Robot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 06:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/tags/sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Operations Studio</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2018/01/14/sql-operations-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2018/01/14/sql-operations-studio/</guid>
      <description>SQL Operations Studio Released Microsoft recently released a preview of a free, new SQL management suite called SQL Operations Studio.
It is obviously based on Visual Studio Code, so is extensible and scriptable, and potentially the SQL Operations Studio features may be added to VSCode later.
The product already has an incredibly useful, customizable dashboard feature, as well as support for viewing SQL Query Plans and Execution Plans.
There is also a connection manager that handles Azure connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server Management Studio is Free</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2017/02/02/sql-server-management-studio-is-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2017/02/02/sql-server-management-studio-is-free/</guid>
      <description>SQL Server Management Studio aka SSMS is available to download and use for free from Microsoft. You do not require a SQL Server license.
The latest version of SSMS, and future versions, are available from here:
https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/mt238290.aspx
This makes this easier for developers and DBAs that want to work with SQL Server, without having to acquire and install a full, licensed SQL Server ISO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding duplicated data across one or more columns in a database table</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/02/28/finding-duplicated-data-across-one-or-more-columns-in-a-database-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 10:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2009/02/28/finding-duplicated-data-across-one-or-more-columns-in-a-database-table/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few months ago I posted a little query about &lt;a title=&#34;Finding duplicate rows in a database table&#34; href=&#34;http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/2008/10/17/finding-duplicate-rows-in-the-database/&#34; target=&#34;\_blank&#34;&gt;finding duplicate rows in a database table&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;m revisiting this because I helped out Doogie with a similar query last night but with some complications. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the original simple scenario of checking duplicates in a single column. Some example data, a Users table: &lt;pre&gt;+-&amp;mdash;+-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;mdash;+ | Id | Email | +-&amp;mdash;+-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;mdash;+ | 1 | joe@bloggs.com | | 2 | joe@bloggs.com | | 3 | joe@bloggs.com | | 4 | jane@doe.com | | 5 | jane@doe.com | | 6 | john@doe.com | +-&amp;mdash;+-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;ndash;-&amp;mdash;+&lt;/pre&gt; You can see that joe@bloggs.com and jane@doe.com have been duplicated. This could have been prevented by putting a unique index on the Email column. So to find what emails have duplicates in our table:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding duplicate rows in the database</title>
      <link>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/17/finding-duplicate-rows-in-the-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sadrobot.co.nz/blog/2008/10/17/finding-duplicate-rows-in-the-database/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This post has been re-visited in Finding duplicated data across one or more columns in a database table
Information gleaned from Microsoft KB article: How to remove duplicate rows from a table in SQL Server
When you allow duplicated rows in a database that aren&amp;rsquo;t expected and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be allowed, it&amp;rsquo;s a flag saying that you need a unique index on the table to prevent duplicate rows to be added in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>